sassyhongkong.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Sassy Hong Kong

_Last Modified: May 18, 2018_

This privacy policy ( _together with our  [Website Terms and Conditions](https://www.sassyhongkong.com/terms-of-use/) and any other documents referred in it_) sets out the basis for processing any personal data we collect from you or that you provide to us. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data. By using our website [www.sassyhongkong.com](https://www.sassyhongkong.com/) ( _our ‘Website’_ ) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

Depending on the purpose for which you are providing your personal data, for the purpose of the Data Protection Act ( _the ‘Act’_ ), the data controller ( _or entity responsible for the data collected_ ) will be us. Within the context of this policy ‘we’ mean Sassy Media Group.

**Data we may collect from you:**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

_Information acquired/provided through our Website:_

  * This includes information provided when subscribing to our services, participating in social media functions, or requesting further services.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. If you send us personal information which identifies you via email, we may keep your email and email address. We may also collect information that is available from your browser.
  * We may ask you to complete optional surveys for research purposes.
  * Details of your visits to the Websites including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access.
  * We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**How we use your data:**

Your data will only be used for the purposes indicated when you submit the data or as detailed under this privacy policy.

_We use personal information held about you in the following ways:_

  * To update and enhance our records
  * To improve our Website ( _to ensure the content from the Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer; we continuously strive to improve our website based on the feedback we receive from you_ )
  * To send weekly newsletters
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey, research studies and/or market research activity, or any other site feature

**Disclosure of your data:**

The email address you provided, will be used to send you our weekly newsletters, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

We will not transfer any of your data to any third parties without your permission or unless indicated in this privacy policy or agreed by you on a form on the Website.

_We may disclose your personal information to third parties without obtaining further consent from you including:_

  * Where we outsource any of our business functions under which we collect or store your data, in which case we will ensure that any such service provider adheres to at least the same obligations of security with regard to your data as undertaken by us
  * Where we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety of our employees, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We will never sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information for marketing.

**Where we store your data:**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ( _‘EEA’_ ). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Your rights:**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you ( _before collecting your data_ ) if we wish to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes and request your consent to these activities.

If you wish to change your mailing preferences or opt-out of specific marketing communications sent from Sassy Media Group, you may notify us via our ‘Contact Us’ form. Alternatively, you may contact us on +852 3996 8297. It may take up to 21 days for the changes to come into effect. Please note that this will not alter your current email subscription preferences.

**Access to information:**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee ( _as amended from time to time_ ) to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

If you would like to request a copy of your personal data under the Act or have any other related queries, please email [privacy@sassymediagroup.com](mailto:privacy@sassymediagroup.com).

**Accuracy:**

We will take reasonable steps to create an accurate record of any personal data you have submitted. However, we do not assume responsibility for confirming the ongoing accuracy of your personal data. You can update your personal data by emailing us at [privacy@sassymediagroup.com](mailto:privacy@sassymediagroup.com) . Please note that it may take up to 21 days for the changes to come into effect.

**Cookies:**

This website use cookies.  By using this website, and agreeing to this policy, you consent to Sassy Media Group’s use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

### **About cookies:**

Cookies are files sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.  This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies.  Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

**Cookies on our website:**

_Sassy Media Group uses the following cookies on this website, for the following purposes:_

  * Google Analytics

**Google cookies**

Sassy Media Group uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on the users’ computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website.  Google will store and use this information.  Google’s privacy policy is available at [www.google.com/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

Some of our marketing and advertising partners may use cookies on our site. Our marketing and advertising partners may include, but are not limited to Google AdWords, Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Microsoft Bing.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology related to the advertisements and/or links that appear on Sassy Media Group’s website, and sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( _such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons_ ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalise the advertising content that you see.

Sassy Media Group has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Sassy Media Group’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Terms and Conditions:**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Website Terms and Conditions](https://www.sassyhongkong.com/terms-of-use/) _._

**Your consent:**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. By continuing to use our Website you will be deemed to have accepted such changes.

**Contact:**

Questions, comments, and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed. You may contact us using the information below:

**Sassy Media Group** , 25/F Arion Commercial Centre, 2-12 Queens Road West, Sheung Wan, Hong Kong, [privacy@sassymediagroup.com](mailto:privacy@sassymediagroup.com)

_Email subscription image credits: image 1 courtesy of[Chris Ralston](https://unsplash.com/@thisisralston) via [Unsplash](https://unsplash.com/photos/09HGdZzkP-Q), image 2 courtesy of [From This Position](https://www.instagram.com/from_this_position/) via [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/p/BsCpWhOgLv4/), image 3 courtesy of [Sergey Nazarov](https://www.gettyimages.com/search/photographer?family=creative&photographer=Sergey+Nazarov) via [Getty](https://www.gettyimages.com/detail/photo/young-people-with-glasses-of-champagne-at-christmas-royalty-free-image/879298768), image 4 courtesy of [Marion Michele](https://unsplash.com/@marion_michele) via [Unsplash](https://unsplash.com/photos/xwQojkzmsHM)_
